module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which medication is an antihistamine?', 
    a: 'Lamisil',
    b: 'Tylenol',
    c: 'Benadryl',
    d: 'Motrin',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The vertical bar key on a keyboard, "|" is also referred to as what?', 
    a: 'Pipe Symbol',
    b: 'Harp Key',
    c: 'Bar Symbol',
    d: 'Straight Slash Key',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a component of a toilet?', 
    a: 'Flapper',
    b: 'Float',
    c: 'Fill Valve',
    d: 'Tub Ring',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of creature was Gizmo from the movie "Gremlims"?', 
    a: 'Gelfling',
    b: 'Mogwai',
    c: 'Na\'vi',
    d: 'Zokzah',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following animals is a carnivore?', 
    a: 'Whale',
    b: 'Deer',
    c: 'Chimpanzee',
    d: 'Caterpillar',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Luigi\'s last name from the Mario Bros. video game franchise?' , 
    a: 'Miyamoto',
    b: 'Mario',
    c: 'DiNapoli',
    d: 'Esposito',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where was pizza invented?', 
    a: 'Bronx, New York',
    b: 'Brooklyn, New York',
    c: 'Florence, Italy',
    d: 'Naples, Italy',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'President Clinton and his family had a pet named Socks. What kind of pet was it?', 
    a: 'Ferret',
    b: 'Cat',
    c: 'Rabbit',
    d: 'Dog',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which part of the plant/tree is cinnamon made out of?', 
    a: 'The Flower',
    b: 'The Stem',
    c: 'The Root',
    d: 'The Bark',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which item is seen in the famous painting "The Birth of Venus"?', 
    a: 'Scallop Shell',
    b: 'Harp',
    c: 'Serpent',
    d: 'White Horse',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
